The day of the new starry sky
The twinkling of the shining sun
Bikiniku-san
In the basket, I have a lunch and a dream
Of course, I'll always be with you
See, I can't help but feel like I'm diving
That's right, I'm happy
Because I have friends with you in the sky
I laugh when I'm at the hotel
The time of the twinkling of the shining sun
The twinkling of the shining sun
With you, with you, with you
If I make a dream come true
The shape of my heart will overlap
It's a great feeling
Muka Muka
Shoryu Baby is born
This is Takagaya
There are a lot of mansions on the right side of the station
It may not be true, but in the past there were only fields and fields
But the opposite side of the station is the same as it was
There was this Takagaya shopping mall in front of the station
It's like being forgotten in the middle of the city
This shopping mall is my town
And this pet shop is my house
My father is a replacement
It's a shop that sells precious things
What's this? A bird's egg?
This is not a bird's egg, bird's egg, or a man's egg
So what?
Well...
So what do you mean?
I don't know, but I bought it because it's rare
It's not that it's rare
How much is it?
It's 30,000 yen
30,000 yen?
I don't know what kind of egg it is, but it's 30,000 yen?
Don't say that
Last time, Uiwa cried because the bird's egg died
So I thought she'd be happy
Bye-bye
Oh, she's back
Sanpei, how are you?
I'm fine
Uiwa, I bought you a souvenir
A souvenir?
Wow, it's a huge egg
Isn't it amazing?
How many people would have thought it would be?
What do you mean?
What kind of egg is this?
This egg is alive
Is it alive?
And it cost 30,000 yen
There's a lot of life in it
See?
You can hear the heartbeat
I can't hear anything
What do you mean?
Ryo-chan?
What?
I'm fine
I bought it because I heard it was alive
Did you just hear it?
No, so...
Hey, answer me
Anybody home?
30,000 yen
Your dad was fooled again
Well, don't worry
Just think you studied well
What did you say?
Your dad thought he'd be happy
Instead of the bird's egg
He cried so much
The egg is alive
At that time
The egg that I thought it was going to be born
I was so sad and sad
But I didn't expect it
I cried because I didn't expect it
It's so cool
I'm looking forward to it
I'll show you the egg
That's right
Ryo-chan, don't go home
I paid 30,000 yen
Definitely
What a strange couple
All right
Is this enough?
Yes, just keep it
Are you really okay?
You want to return the egg, right?
You're going to feel like a mother
Stretch out your senses
Yes
Mother, mother
Welcome
Did you let me go in that dress?
What?
Isn't it cute?
I can't believe it
How's it going?
It's good
But I'm going to buy some cigarettes first
Why?
Did you get rid of Ryo-chan?
Mr. Tsu-zu
Did you just drink it?
Thank you for watching
Congratulations on being a man
No, no
I'm going to throw up the cigarettes
That's right
Mr. Tsu-zu
I'm home
What's wrong?
Hazuki
Your father is in trouble
Is he dead?
No, no
He was born
What do you mean he was born?
After all, until he was born
I decided to quit smoking and alcohol
Really?
That's right
Who is he?
No one
You're the only one
I thought you were a man
Don't you understand?
You're not stupid
Why do you have to be a man?
Everyone says that
I saw it too
Men don't have to be a man
Senta is a real idiot
A real idiot
I don't like you
Good morning
What?
Do you know what a man is?
I don't know
Do you want to die?
Idiot
What's going on?
Shut up
What are you thinking about with your father?
About a man
You go there
Uiwa
Your father has an egg
It's a copy
A copy?
What's that?
It's a mystery egg
A mystery egg?
Russia is a famous monster
My father told me
You know it, right?
My father went to Russia
Copy
Mom
Aren't you eating too much?
He's hungry
We have to eat and take care of him
I feel like I want some sour fruit
Mom
Do you have any lemon?
Dad
Aren't you hungry?
It's heavy
I'm hungry now
Really?
I'm really hungry
Yay
I'm going to be born
You-chan, are you okay?
Dad
It's a dream
What?
It's falling
It's hard
It's broken
It's alive
Are you okay?
It's a dream
Stop it
What's wrong?
The egg
Dad, do something
You're born
You-chan, are you okay?
Yay
It hurts, but I'm born
Stop it
No, I'm going to eat your nose
I know it's a breakfast
Give me some vegetables
Okay
What's your name?
Muka Muka
Muka Muka?
That's a nice name
It's cute that I'm the only one who's hungry
Where is it?
Muka Muka
You're hungry
I'm fine
I'm sleepy
I'm going to bed
Good night
What's wrong with him?
He looks like his mother
Mother?
I'm his mother?
It's the same as a bird
I think the bird is the mother who saw the bird from the egg
It's called a bird's nest
It looks like a bird
It can't be helped
Leave it to Muka Muka
Muka Muka seems to be asleep
It's good that she's adopted by her mother
No way
Muka Muka
One, two, three, four, five
Good morning, Muka
Good morning
Muka Muka
What are you doing?
You can't do it
I'm the only one who can do it
Muka Muka
Don't you want to get away from me?
But you can't come to school
If you come to school and make a fuss
I'll be in trouble
What are you doing?
You have a pumpkin
Hey
Do you like this blueberry jam so much?
I see
Mom, do you have a blueberry jam?
I have a pumpkin, but I don't think so
I just opened it yesterday
Yes
Just a minute
No
I have to be quiet
Muka Muka
Good morning
I know
I'm waiting for you
Okay, Midori-chan, it's time for dinner
I'm going
Muka Muka
Fuiwa, good morning
Tsukine, good morning
What are you doing so early?
I'm going to run
What?
What is this?
Muka Muka
Yes, it's called Muka Muka
So what is this?
Fuiwa, what are you doing?
It's a big lizard
A lizard?
Isn't it Godzilla?
Why?
What is this?
It's a rare animal
I was born late
So yesterday's eggs
Yes
I'm sure it's not a copy
Did you believe that joke?
Uiwa is my mother
Mother?
Uiwa?
Are you Godzilla's mother?
No, I just got a job
Three claws?
Is it a bee?
I think so
What?
Three claws means
A dinosaur
A dinosaur?
The characteristic of a dinosaur is that it has three claws
I see, it was a dinosaur
Yes!
Mother!
Muka Muka, it was a dinosaur
Really?
I'm sure it's because it's a fox
It's an animal
It's cool, it's a dinosaur
I wonder if it's an old man
A dinosaur?
It's a dinosaur
It's fine
It's not sleeping
Really?
You'll wake up if you pull it
No, I'll let you sleep
Otherwise you can't go to school
It's a dinosaur
The world has changed
A dinosaur?
Gau!
Mua!
Shenta
You're getting worried about that dinosaur
Shenta, you promised to keep quiet about Muka Muka
If everyone knows, it'll be a big fuss
I know, but as a mother
I'm not a mother!
So, I'm still asleep.
Please wait until the mother Uiba comes home.
What?
Oh, it's mother's home!
Mother?
Uiba, you're Kyoryu-chan, aren't you?
No, I don't think so.
It's fine. It's fine.
It seems that mother is not here.
She seems to like Kyoryu-chan.
Huh? Is he still asleep?
It's true. He's still asleep.
Huh?
Isn't he getting bigger?
By the way,
he said he would grow up to sleep.
Huh?
Did Uiba understand that Uiba came home?
Again?
Do something!
You really like it, don't you?
You say you like it when you don't like it.
Huh?
No, I don't.
Anyway, everyone wants to see you.
Take her away.
Huh?
Anyway, Muka Muka has become a member of our Shikatanite.
Please take care of her.
Would you like to have a drink with your relatives?
Dad, are you okay if you drink alcohol?
Huh?
I did it.
Isn't it crazy?
Is he having a bad temper?
Yes.
Muka Muka!
Stop it!
Oh no! He's back!
Oh no!
Ryo-chan!
Mika!
You can catch him!
Everyone, please take care of him!
Hey!
Wait!
Hey! Don't slip!
Yeah! Help me!
I'll kill you!
Yeah, he's a good boy.
Take him away.
Hey!
Wait!
Yeah!
Dad's drinking alcohol, so he's not drunk anymore!
I'm sorry.
There he is!
Oh yeah!
Shibiria-san, please give me a blueberry jam.
Huh?
Um...
Here it is!
Muka Muka!
Huh?
He's gone quiet.
Oh no!
You're Muka Muka's mother-in-law, aren't you?
I told you I wasn't pregnant!
Let's play, Ryo.
This guy...
Why am I the mother-in-law of that dinosaur?
Are you mad?
Oh no!
Good night.
Fire Fire Fire Fire Fire Fire Fire Paradise
Come, come, come, come, come, come, come, come, come!
See?
We're friends.
Let's play, Ryo.
It's because I'm the heart of this planet!
Fire, fire, fire, fire, fire, party!
Let's do it!
I like it, I like it, I like it, I like it, I like it, I like it!
Everyone, let's have fun on a day like this!
Let's play with each other!
The End
I understand that Mukamuka likes sweets.
There's no doubt that she's a child-loving dinosaur.
I'm sure she's not thinking about anything.
But as a mother-in-law, I want to say something.
Don't make eye contact with people who are in danger!
Next time on Mukamuka Paradise,
I'll be waiting for you on Valentine's Day!
Mukamuka!